A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 8 FA1416
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 8
1981-2011
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA1416
45.85 Cubic Feet 118 document boxes, 1 legal document box. 1 1/2 document box
Scope and Contents
The collection contains Grant Files and associated administrative records.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Arranged as received
- Johns Hopkins University, Center of Excellence (Renewal), Linda P. Fried (2007-0005), 2007-2010 (Box 537, Folder 4013)
- University of Chicago, Hartford Geriatrics Center of Excellence, Greg A. Sachs (2003-0201), 2003-2007 (Box 537, Folder 4014)
- University of Chicago, Center of Excellence in Geriatric Medicine and Training, Greg A. Sachs (2006-0168), 2006-2011 (Box 537, Folder 4015)
- University of Rochester, Center of Excellence (Renewal), William J. Hall (2007-0008), 2007-2011 (Box 537, Folder 4016)
- University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio, Center of Excellence in Geriatric Medicine and Training, David V. Espino (2006-0171), 2006, 2008-2010 (Box 537, Folder 4017)
- American Lung Association, Dalsemer Scholars Program, James Swomley & L. Clayton (82614-1X), 1981-1987, 1989, 2000 (Box 537, Folder 4018-4019)
- American Lung Association, Dalsemer Scholars Program, James Swomley & L. Clayton (82614-1X), 1981-1987, 1989, 2000 (Box 538, Folder 4020)
- University of California, San Diego School of Medicine, Biotechnology Transfer Program, Robert G. Petersdorf (84412-0), 1984-1988 (Box 538, Folder 4021-4023)
- University of California, San Diego School of Medicine, Biotechnology Transfer Program, Review, Robert G. Petersdorf (84412-0), 1985-1987 (Box 538, Folder 4024)
- Educational Broadcasting Corporation, Who Lives, Who Dies, Roger E. Weisberg (87355-0), 1986-1989 (Box 538, Folder 4025)
- Educational Broadcasting Corporation, Who Lives, Who Dies, Roger E. Weisberg (87355-0), 1986-1989 (Box 539, Folder 4026)
- Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information, Project to Develop and Implement Statewide Community Health Information System in Minnesota, Dale V. Shaller (93142-H), 1992-1996 (Box 539, Folder 4027-4028)
- Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information, Project to Develop and Implement Statewide Community Health Information System in Minnesota, Dale V. Shaller (93142-H), Attachments, 1993-1994, 1997-1999 (Box 539, Folder 4029-4030)
- Red Cross Disaster Relief, Delbert C. Staley (89301-0), 1989-1990 (Box 539, Folder 4031)
- The Colorado Health Care Purchasing Alliance, Inc., Positioning Coalitions for the Age of Reform, Louise Y. Probst (93345-H), 1993-1996 (Box 540, Folder 4032-4033)
- Dartmouth Medical School, A Demonstration Project of Patient Informed Decision Making: Patients with Benign Hypertrophy of the Prostate (Renewal), John Wennberg (87066-3H), 1987-1991 (Box 540, Folder 4034-4037)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Product Development Activities of the Foundation Informed Medical Decision Making, John Wennberg (89302-H), 1989-1991 (Box 541, Folder 4038)
- Foundation for Health Care Quality, Health Care Effectiveness Information Utility-Obstetrics Quality and Access Demonstration Project, Keith McCandless (90057-H), 1989-1993 (Box 541, Folder 4039-4040)
- Foundation for Informed Decision Making, Development of Shared Decision Making Programs and Business Planning, Joseph F. Kasper (91114-H), 1991-1993 (Box 541, Folder 4041-4042)
- Foundation for Informed Decision Making, Development of Shared Decision Making Programs and Business Planning, Joseph F. Kasper (91114-H), 1991-1993 (Box 542, Folder 4043)
- Foundation for Informed Medical Decision Making, Project Related Investment, Joseph F. Kasper (92288-H), 1992-1995 (Box 542, Folder 4044-4045)
- George Washington University, National Health Forum, Meetings on Topics Related to Health Care and Quality, Judith Miller Jones (87341-2H), 1987-1990 (Box 542, Folder 4046-4047)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, Ira C. Magaziner (91233-G), 1991-1995 (Box 542, Folder 4048)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, Ira C. Magaziner (91233-G), 1991-1995 (Box 543, Folder 4049-4050)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, Site Visit, Ira C. Magaziner (91233-G), 1992 (Box 543, Folder 4051)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000, Directions for Elder Care in Rhode Island, 1991 (Box 543, Folder 4052)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, James Thomas (93354-G), 1993-1995 (Box 543, Folder 4053-4054)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, James Thomas (93354-G), 1993-1995 (Box 544, Folder 4055-4058)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, Edward Zesk (94125-G), 1993-1996 (Box 544, Folder 4059-4061)
- Interfaith Health Care Ministries, Aging 2000: Systemic Change in Care for the Elderly in Rhode Island, Site Visit, Edward Zesk (94125-G), 1995 (Box 545, Folder 4063)
- Harvard Medical School, Hartford Geriatrics in Primary Care Initiative, Thomas Inui (94146-G), 1994-1998 (Box 545, Folder 4064-4066)
- Harvard Medical School, Hartford Geriatrics in Primary Care Initiative, Thomas Inui (94146-G), 1993-1998 (Box 546, Folder 4067-4069)
- Harvard Medical School, Hartford Geriatrics in Primary Care Initiative, Evaluation, Thomas Inui (94146-G), 1996-1998 (Box 546, Folder 4070)
- Harvard Medical School, Hartford Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Proposal (94146-G), 1994 (Box 546, Folder 4071)
- National Forum on Quality Improvements to Health Care, 1990 (Box 546, Folder 4072)
- National Forum for Quality Improvements to Health Care, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 547, Folder 4073-4075)
- Stanford University, The Efficacy of Physical Therapy in Preserving Function in Hospitalized Elderly, Carol Winograd (89000-3G), 1989-1993 (Box 547, Folder 4076-4077)
- Stanford University, The Efficacy of Physical Therapy in Preserving Function in Hospitalized Elderly, Carol Winograd (89000-3G), 1989-1993 (Box 548, Folder 4048-4080)
- Stanford University, The Efficacy of Physical Therapy in Preserving Function in Hospitalized Elderly, Operations Manual, Carol Winograd (89000-3G), 1990 (Box 548, Folder 4081-4082)
- St. Marys Hospital Medical Center, Reducing Functional Deterioration in the Hospitalized Elderly Patient, Mark Sager (89031-3G), 1989-1993 (Box 548, Folder 4083-4084)
- St. Marys Hospital Medical Center, Reducing Functional Deterioration in the Hospitalized Elderly Patient, Mark Sager (89031-3G), 1989-1993 (Box 549, Folder 4085-4088)
- United Health Services, System Care Management, Linda J. Battaglini (92211-G), 1991-1996 (Box 549, Folder 4089-4090)
- United Health Services, System Care Management, Linda J. Battaglini (92211-G), 1991-1996 (Box 550, Folder 4091-4093)
- United Health Services, System Care Management, Evaluation, Linda J. Battaglini (92211-G), 1982, 1990-1991, 1993, 1996 (Box 550, Folder 4094-4095)
- United Health Services, System Care Management, Site Visit, Linda J. Battaglini (92211-G), 1992-1994 (Box 550, Folder 4096)
- United Health Services, System Care Management, Site Visit, Linda J. Battaglini (92211-G), 1993-1994 (Box 551, Folder 4097)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Geriatric Pharmacology Scholarships for Medical Studies, Harold Epstein (89352-G), 1989-1995, 1997 (Box 551, Folder 4098-4100)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Gero-Physician-Scientist Development Program, Harold Epstein (90289-G), 1990-1996 (Box 551, Folder 4101-4102)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Gero-Physician-Scientist Development Program, Harold Epstein (90289-G), 1990-1996 (Box 552, Folder 4103-4104)
- Brigham & Women's Hospital, Improving Medication Use Among The Nation's Elderly: Defining the Problem and Identifying Solutions, Jerry Avorn (92031-G), 1992-1995 (Box 552, Folder 4105-4108)
- Brigham & Women's Hospital, Meeting on Drugs and the Elderly, Jerry Avorn (92031-G), 1992 November 4, 1993 July 7 (Box 553, Folder 4109-4110)
- Brigham & Women's Hospital, Expert Panel on Medication Use and the Elderly, Jerry Avorn (92031-G), 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 553, Folder 4111)
- Brigham & Women's Hospital, Publications on Improving Medication Use Among The Nation's Elderly: Defining the Problem and Identifying Solutions, Jerry Avorn (92031-G), 1992-1993 (Box 553, Folder 4112)
- Brigham & Women's Hospital, Advisory Groups on Improving Medication Use Among The Nation's Elderly: Defining the Problem and Identifying Solutions, Jerry Avorn (92031-G), 1992-1993 (Box 553, Folder 4113-4114)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Robert L. Luchi (95218-G), 1994-1998 (Box 554, Folder 4115-4116)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Evaluation, Robert L. Luchi (95218-G), 1995-1997 (Box 554, Folder 4117)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Planning Grant Applications, Robert L. Luchi (95218-G), 1995 (Box 554, Folder 4118)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Houston Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), (96201-G), 1998 (Box 554, Folder 4119)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Houston Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Evaluation (96201-G), 1998 (Box 554, Folder 4120)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Increasing the Geriatric Content of Primary Care Residency Training (94142-G), 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 554, Folder 4121)
- Boston University, Center of Excellence in Geriatrics, Patricia Barry (97269-G), 1996-2001 (Box 554, Folder 4122)
- Boston University, Center of Excellence in Geriatrics, Patricia Barry (97269-G), 1996-2001 (Box 555, Folder 4123-4125)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, "Prehab" Project Coordinating Center, Hospital Outcomes Project for the Elderly (HOPE), Curt D. Furberg (89227-G), 1989-1993 (Box 555, Folder 4126-4128)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, "Prehab" Project Coordinating Center, Hospital Outcomes Project for the Elderly (HOPE), Curt D. Furberg (89227-G), 1989-1993 (Box 556, Folder 4129-4133)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Project for the Elderly (HOPE), Monthly Recruitment Summaries, Curt D. Furberg (89227-G), 1990-1991 (Box 556, Folder 4134)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Project for the Elderly (HOPE), Descriptive Analyses, Curt D. Furberg (89227-G), 1995-1996 (Box 556, Folder 4135)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Center for Excellence Designation Awards, William R. Hazzard (97257-G), 1997-1998, 2000 (Box 557, Folder 4136)
- Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, Physical Deconditioning a Treatable Source of Functional Loss in Acutely Hospitalized Older Adults, Hilary Siebens (89005-3G), 1989-1993 (Box 557, Folder 4137-4139)
- Harvard Medical School, Center for Excellence, Lewis A. Lipsitz (990340), 1999-2004 (Box 557, Folder 4140-4142)
- Health Policy Corporation of Iowa, Development and Application of the Next Generation of Quality of Care Management Technology, Sal Bognanni (88330-H), 1988-1992 (Box 558, Folder 4143-4146)
- Health Policy Corporation of Iowa, Establishing a Community Health Management System in Des Moines/Central Iowa Golden Circle, Sal Bognanni (91115-H), 1991-1993 (Box 558, Folder 4147-4149)
- Health Policy Corporation of Iowa, Establishing a Community Health Management System in Des Moines/Central Iowa Golden Circle, Sal Bognanni (91115-H), 1991-1993 (Box 559, Folder 4150)
- Health Policy Corporation of Iowa, Strengthening Community Health Reform in Iowa, Paul M. Pietzsch (92213-H), 1992-1995 (Box 559, Folder 4151-4154)
- Henry Ford Health System, Complementary Geriatric Generalist Practice Model, Nancy A. Whitelaw (93042-G), 1993-1998 (Box 559, Folder 4155)
- Henry Ford Health System, Complementary Geriatric Generalist Practice Model, Nancy A. Whitelaw (93042-G), 1993-1998 (Box 560, Folder 4156-4158)
- Henry Ford Health System, Complementary Geriatric Generalist Practice Model, Site Visit, Nancy A. Whitelaw (93042-G), 1992-1994 (Box 560, Folder 4159-4160)
- Henry Ford Health System, Complementary Geriatric Generalist Practice Model, Nancy A. Whitelaw (93042-G), 1992-1993 (Box 560, Folder 4161-4162)
- Henry Ford Health System, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nancy A. Whitelaw (95220-G), 1995-1997 (Box 560, Folder 4163)
- Henry Ford Health System, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nancy A. Whitelaw (95220-G), 1995-1997 (Box 561, Folder 4164)
- Indiana University, Medication Used and Depressed Elderly Patients in Primary Care, William M. Tierney (89355-G), 1989-1994 (Box 561, Folder 4165-4170)
- Indiana University, Medication Used and Depressed Elderly Patients in Primary Care, More Appendices to the Proposal, William M. Tierney (89355-G), 1990 (Box 562, Folder 4171)
- Indiana University, Coordination of a Unified Set of Standards for Health Care Information Messages, Clement J. McDonald (92196-H), 1992-1997 (Box 562, Folder 4172-4174)
- Indiana University, Coordination of a Unified Set of Standards for Health Care Information Messages, Progress Report and Attachments, Clement J. McDonald (92196-H), 1994-1995 (Box 562, Folder 4175-4177)
- Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, Design Structured Approach to Medical Practices Guidelines, Marilyn Field (90025-H), 1989-1992 (Box 563, Folder 4178-4180)
- Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, Committee for the Patient Record, 1988-1990 (Box 563, Folder 4180-4182)
- Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, Committee for the Patient Record, 1989-1990 (Box 564, Folder 4184-4185)
- Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, Overcoming Impediments to Regional Data Repositories, Kathleen N. Lohr (91281-H), 1991-1994 (Box 564, Folder 4186-4188)
- Abt Health Care Foundation, The Effect of Type of Insurance on the Use and Cost of Health Care Among Frail Elderly, Laurance Branch (93339-G), 1992-1997 (Box 564, Folder 4189)
- Abt Health Care Foundation, The Effect of Type of Insurance on the Use and Cost of Health Care Among Frail Elderly, Laurance Branch (93339-G), 1992-1997 (Box 565, Folder 4190)
- Abt Health Care Foundation, The Effect of Type of Insurance on the Use and Cost of Health Care Among Frail Elderly, Evaluation, Laurance Branch (93339-G), 1995 (Box 565, Folder 4191)
- Abt Health Care Foundation, The Effect of Type of Insurance on the Use and Cost of Health Care Among Frail Elderly, Product, Laurance Branch (93339-G), 1995 (Box 565, Folder 4192)
- American Geriatrics Society, Academic Geriatrics Program Development, Linda Barondess (88278-G), 1988-1992 (Box 565, Folder 4193-4196)
- American Geriatrics Society, Academic Geriatrics Program Development, Linda Barondess (88278-G), 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 566, Folder 4197)
- American Geriatrics Society, Planning Meeting for Academic Geriatrics Program Development Workshop, 1989 (Box 566, Folder 4198)
- Beth Israel Hospital, Medications and Aging: Research and Education in Geriatric Pharmacology, Jerry Avorn (88220-3G), 1988-1993 (Box 566, Folder 4199-4203)
- Beth Israel Hospital, Medications and Aging: Research and Education in Geriatric Pharmacology, Jerry Avorn (88220-3G), 1988-1992 (Box 567, Folder 4204)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1992-1996 (Box 567, Folder 4205-4208)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Descriptive Analysis, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1995 (Box 567, Folder 4209)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Investigators' Meeting, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1990-1991 (Box 568, Folder 4210)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Interim Investigators' Meeting, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1990 (Box 568, Folder 4211)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Meta Analysis, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1990 (Box 568, Folder 4212)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Prehab Meta Analysis Investigators, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1989 (Box 568, Folder 4213)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Site Visit, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 568, Folder 4214)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Treatment Effects, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1993 (Box 568, Folder 4215)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Data Packet, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1990 (Box 568, Folder 4216)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Data Packet, Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1991 (Box 569, Folder 4217)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Data Packet (Phase I), Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1991 (Box 569, Folder 4218)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly Analysis (HOPE), Data Packet (Phase II), Timothy M. Morgan (92312-G), 1991-1992 (Box 569, Folder 4219)
- Bowman Gray School of Medicine, Hospital Outcomes Projects for the Elderly (HOPE), Investigators' Meeting (89227), 1990-1991 (Box 569, Folder 4220)
- Brandeis University, Development of a National Strategy for Strengthening Long Term Care for the Elderly, Walter Leutz (87221-G), 1987-1991 (Box 569, Folder 4221-4223)
- Brandeis University, Development of a National Strategy for Strengthening Long Term Care for the Elderly, Walter Leutz (87221-G), 1987-1991 (Box 570, Folder 4224-4226)
- Brandeis University, Development of a National Strategy for Strengthening Long Term Care for the Elderly, Washington, D. C., Walter Leutz (87221-G), 1989 March 15 (Box 570, Folder 4227)
- Brandeis University, Development of a National Strategy for Strengthening Long Term Care for the Elderly, Site Visit, Walter Leutz (87221-G), 1987-1988 (Box 570, Folder 4228)
- Brandeis University, Development of a National Strategy for Strengthening Long Term Care for the Elderly, Advisory Panel Meeting-Long Term Care, Walter Leutz (87221-G), 1987-1989 (Box 570, Folder 4229)
- Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center, Inc., Community-base Acute Care (CAC), John R. Burton (94032-G), 1994-1996 (Box 571, Folder 4230-4234)
- Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center, Inc., Community-base Acute Care (CAC), Evaluation, Baltimore, John R. Burton (94032-G), 1994-1995 (Box 571, Folder 4235)
- Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center, Inc., Community-base Acute Care (CAC), Advisory Committee Meeting, John R. Burton (94032-G), 1994 (Box 571, Folder 4236)
- Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center, Inc., Community-base Acute Care (CAC), Hospital Without Walls (HWW), John R. Burton (94032-G), 1993 (Box 571, Folder 4237)
- Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center, Inc., Community-base Acute Care (CAC), Hospital Without Walls (HWW), John R. Burton (94032-G), 1993 (Box 572, Folder 4238)
- Foundation Administered Project, Prehab, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 572, Folder 4239-4241)
- N.Y. Community Trust, Center for Policy on Aging, Study of Changing Lifestyles, Quality of Life and Quality of Care of New York City Elderly, Barry Gurland (89085-2G), 1989-1992 (Box 572, Folder 4242-4244)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, State of California's Section 1115 Waiver Request, 1982 (Box 573, Folder 4245)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Demonstration of Prepaid Financing for Long-Term Care of Frail Elderly, Richard Zawadski (83107-3H), 1983-1987, 1989 (Box 573, Folder 4246-4249)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Demonstration of Prepaid Financing for Long-Term Care of Frail Elderly, Additional Information, Richard Zawadski (83107-3H), 1981-1985, 1988-1989 (Box 574, Folder 4250)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Demonstration of Prepaid Financing for Long-Term Care of Frail Elderly, Meeting, 1988 April 13, Richard Zawadski (83107-3H), 1987-1988 (Box 574, Folder 4251)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Demonstration of Prepaid Financing for Long-Term Care of Frail Elderly, Meeting, 1988 July 8-14, Richard Zawadski (83107-3H), 1987-1988 (Box 574, Folder 4252)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, The Risk-Based A Community Care Organization for Dependent Adults (CCODA), Reports, 1981-1986, 1989-1990 (Box 574, Folder 4253-4254)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, On Lok News, 1988-1992 (Box 574, Folder 4255)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Reports, 1987 (Box 574, Folder 4256)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi -Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Marie-Louise Ansak (89016-3G), 1986-1990 (Box 575, Folder 4257-4259)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk Long-Term Care, Reports, Marie-Louise Anask (87016-3G), 1987-1989 (Box 575, Folder 4260-4262)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, 2nd Annual Conference on Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Marie-Louise Anask (87016-3G), 1988 July 13-15 (Box 576, Folder 4263)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Richard Zawadski (87016-G), 1986-1987 (Box 576, Folder 4264)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Database Files, 1987-1988 (Box 576, Folder 4265)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Reports, 1988 (Box 576, Folder 4266)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Marie-Louise Ansak (89351-G), 1989-1992 (Box 576, Folder 4267-4268)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Evaluation Site Visit, Marie-Louise Ansak (89351-G), 1988, 1991 (Box 577, Folder 4269)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Supplementary, Marie-Louise Ansak (89351-G), 1989-1990 (Box 577, Folder 4270)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Operational Guidelines, 1990 (Box 577, Folder 4271)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Committee Meeting, 1990 August 15-16 (Box 577, Folder 4272)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Evaluation Site Visit, San Francisco, 1990 January 22, 1989-1990 (Box 577, Folder 4273)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Marie-Louise Ansak, John Shen (91045-G), 1991-1993 (Box 577, Folder 4274-4275)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Proposal, Marie-Louise Ansak, John Shen (91045-G), 1991 (Box 577, Folder 4276)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Committee Meeting, Marie-Louise Ansak, John Shen (91045-G), 1991 (Box 577, Folder 4277)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Site Visit, Marie-Louise Ansak, John Shen (91045-G), 1992 (Box 577, Folder 4278)